ACWA Hyman Blumberg Records 6015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA Hyman Blumberg Records
1932-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Blumberg, Hyman
6015
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records, memorabilia.
5758321
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 11, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collection includes many convention badges, lots of newspaper clippings deteriorating condition. One in Yiddish. Photos are in plastic covered pages of albums or rolled up due to lack of support.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5868 mf: Joseph Schlossberg Additional Papers on Microfilm 5110: Jacob Billikopf New York City Men's Clothing Industry Arbiration Case Files 5670: ACWA Organizer Ida Alter Diaries 5674 OHM: ACWA Master Tapes of Interviews with Retirees 5674 OHT: ACWA Transcripts of Interviews with Retirees 5744: ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5743 P: ACWA Photographs 5107: Decision of the Boards Regarding Hart, Schaffner & Marx, Chicago Industrial Federation of Clothing Manufacturers 5665 mf: ACTWU Fall River Local Minute Books on Microfilm 6015 MB: ACWA Hyman Blumberg Memorabilia 6015 P: ACWA Hyman Blumberg Photographs
Blumberg, Hyman, 1885-1968; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
5758321
- ACWA. Constitution., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution., 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- ACWA. Amalgamated Song Book., Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Song Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Amalgamated Song Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: Copy 2.
- ACWA. 18th Biennial Convention., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 18th Biennial Convention Program and Handbook, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 12-16, 1952.
  - Item 2: 18th Biennial Convention Adopted Resolutions, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: 18th Biennial Convention Adopted Resolutions, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 12-16, 1952. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: 18th Biennial Convention Adopted Resolutions, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 12-16, 1952. Copy 3.
  - Item 5: Report and Audited Financial Statements of the General Office for the Two Years Ended December 31, 1951., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Baltimore Joint Board Convention Dinner; The Traymore, Atlantic City., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 16, 1952.
  - Item 7: 18th Biennial Convention General Executive Board Report, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ACWA. 22th Biennial Convention., 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 22nd Biennial Convention General Executive Board Report, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: May 30-June 3, 1960.
- AFL. Financial Statement., 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: AFL (American Federation of Labor)
    Notes: For Three Months Ending February 28, 1934
- AFL-CIO. 3rd Constitutional Convention., 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Report of AFL-CIO Executive Council to the Third Constitutional Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: AFL-CIO
    Notes: September 19, 1959.
  - Item 2: Third Constitutional Convention Proceedings, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: AFL- CIO
    Notes: September 18, 1959.
  - Item 3: Third Constitutional Convention Proceedings, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 22, 1959.
  - Item 4: Resolutions Booklet no.2, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Resolutions Numbers 68 to 106. September 17-26, 1959
  - Item 5: Report of the Tariff Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 17-26, 1959.
  - Item 6: Committee on the Executive Council Report, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: 1959 Roll Call, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- CIO. 7th Constitutional Convention., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: First Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations)
    Notes: November 20, 1944. Copy 2.
  - Item 2: First Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 20, 1944. Copy 3.
  - Item 3: Second Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 21, 1944.
  - Item 4: Second Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 21, 1944. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: Third Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 22, 1944.
  - Item 6: Third Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 22, 1944. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Report of Committee On Resolutions to the Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 20-24, 1944.
  - Item 8: Report of Committee On Resolutions to the Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 20-24, 1944. Copy 2.
  - Item 9: Report of Committee On Resolutions to the Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: November 20-24, 1944. Copy 3.
  - Item 10: Program Seventh Annual Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Report of President Philip Murray to the Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Philip Murray
    Notes: November 20, 1944.
  - Item 12: Report of President Philip Murray to the Seventh Constitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: First Day Minutes of the Seventh Contstitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CIO. 13th Constitutional Convention., 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Daily Proceeding of the Thirteenth Constitutional Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 5, 1951.
  - Item 2: Daily Proceeding of the Thirteenth Constitutional Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 6, 1951.
  - Item 3: Daily Proceeding of the Thirteenth Constitutional Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 6, 1951. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Daily Proceeding of the Thirteenth Constitutional Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 7, 1951.
  - Item 5: Daily Proceeding of the Thirteenth Constitutional Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 8, 1951.
  - Item 6: Daily Proceeding of the Thirteenth Constitutional Convention, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 9, 1951.
- CIO. 14th Constitutional Convention., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Constitution., 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Memorial Session of the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: As a Tribute to the Life, Works, Memory of Philip Murray. December 3, 1952.
  - Item 3: Memorial Session of the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention., 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: As a Tribute to the Life, Works, Memory of Philip Murray. December 3, 1952. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Program Fourteenth Contstitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 1-5, 1952.
  - Item 5: Daily Proceeding of the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 2, 1952.
  - Item 6: Daily Proceeding of the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 3, 1952.
  - Item 7: Daily Proceeding of the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 3, 1952. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Partial Report of the Resolutions Committee, Fourteenth Constitutional Convetion, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Annual Report, Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: November 17-21, 1952.
  - Item 10: Supplemental Report by the Executive Officers and Vice-Presidents to the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 1, 1952.
  - Item 11: Supplemental Report by the Executive Officers and Vice-Presidents to the Fourteenth Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 1, 1952. Copy 2.
- CIO. 15th Constitutional Convention., 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Daily Proceeding of the Fifteenth Constitutional Convention, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: November 17, 1953.
  - Item 2: Daily Proceeding of the Fifteenth Constitutional Convention, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: November 19, 1953.
- ACA-CIO. Works for Victory., Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: ACA-CIO Works for Victory, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: ACA (American Communicatons Association)
- CIO. Community Services News Letter., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Community Services News Letter, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: National CIO War Relief Committee
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1944:Nov.)
- CIO. Digest of the GI Bill of Rights., Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Digest of the G.I. Bill of Rights (Servicemen's Readjustment Act of 1944), Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Yanks Service Bureau of The Chicago Sun
    Notes: Distributed by The New Veteran.
  - Item 2: Digest of the G.I. Bill of Rights (Servicemen's Readjustment Act of 1944), Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: Distributed by The New Veteran. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Digest of the G.I. Bill of Rights (Servicemen's Readjustment Act of 1944), Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: Distributed by The New Veteran. Copy 3.
- CIO. Economic Outlook., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Economic Outlook, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Department of Research and Education
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1944:Nov.)
- CIO. Facts for Action Pamphlets., Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Labor and Religion, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Facts for Action Pamphlet no.111
  - Item 2: For the Nation's Security, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Facts for Action Pamphlet no.90
- CIO. The New Veteran., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The New Veteran, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.1:no.2/3 (1944:July/Aug.)
  - Item 2: The New Veteran, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.1:no.2/3 (1944:July/Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The New Veteran, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.1:no.2/3 (1944:July/Aug.). Copy 3.
- CIO. Pamphlets., Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: On Every Front CIO Works, Fights, Gives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Wherever He May Be, CIO Helps, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- CIO. Political Primer for All Americans., Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Political Primer for All Americans, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: Facts for Action Pamphlet no.93
  - Item 2: Political Primer for All Americans, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: Facts for Action Pamphlet no.93. Copy 2.
- CIO. Servicemen's Manual., Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: C.I.O. Servicemen's Manual: Facts and Tips for Service Men and Women, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: Public Affairs Committee
    Notes: Public Affairs Pamphlet no.92
- CIO. War Relief News., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: War Relief News, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1944:Oct./Nov.)
  - Item 2: War Relief News, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1944:Oct./Nov.). Copy 2.
- UAW-CIO. GI-Mail, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Fighting and Producing for Democracy at Home and Abroad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Author: War Policy Division, UAW- CIO
    Notes: UAW-CIO GI-Mail. Four blank copies.
- UAW-CIO. Union Counselling., Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Union Counselling: Out of Plant Services for Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
- CMA. International Convention., 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: We Met at the Waldorf: International Convention of the Men's and Boy's Clothing Industry, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: CMA (Clothing Manufacturers Association)
    Notes: October 9-11, 1950.
- Addresses of Discussion Leaders., 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Address of Discussion Leaders on Financing Public Programs of Slum Clearance and Rehousing, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: Harry W. Laidler; Langdon W. Post; Evans Clark; Paul Studenski; Edith Elmer Wood; Harold S. Buttenheim; Joseph P. Day
    Notes: December 15, 1934.
- Boston Clothing Cutters', Trimmers' and Cloth Shrinkers' Union. Diamond Jubilee., 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  ACWA Local 181. 1879-1954.
  - Item 1: Diamond Jubilee, 1879-1954, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Author: Boston Clothing Cutters', Trimmers' and Cloth Shrinkers' Union
    Notes: May 1, 1954.
  - Item 2: Diamond Jubilee, 1879-1954, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 1, 1954. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Diamond Jubilee, 1879-1954, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 1, 1954. Copy 3.
- The Camp of Disappearing Men., 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Camp of Disappearing Men, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Author: John Groth
    Notes: A Story of the Oswiecim Concentration Camp
- Consumer Knowledge Builds Defense., 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Consumer Knowledge Builds Defense, 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Author: Office of Price Administration and Civilian Supply, Consumer Division
    Notes: Bulletin no.11. A Select bibliography of available pamphlet materials. April 1941.
- Decisions of the NLRB., 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Decisions of the National Labor Relations Board, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Author: NLRB (National Labor Relations Board)
    Notes: July 9, 1934 through December 1934.
- Interpretations of the Code of Fair Competition., 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Interpretations of the Code of Fair Competition for the Men's Clothing Industry, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Author: Men's Clothing Authority
  - Item 2: Interpretations of the Code of Fair Competition for the Men's Clothing Industry, 1933; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Labor's Charter of Rights., 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Labor's Charter of Rights, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Author: William Green; Robert F. Wagner; Lloyd K. Garrison; Francis Biddle; Edwin S. Smith; Harry Alvin Millis; Charlton Ogburn
    Notes: Reprinted for American Federationist, April, 1935.
- Long-Range Planning for the Regularization of Industry., 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Long-Range Planning for the Regularization of Industry, 1932; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: J. M. Clark; J. Russell Smith; Edwin S. Smith; George Soule
    Notes: The Report of a Subcommittee of the Committee on Unemployment and Industrial Stabilization of the National Progressive Conference. The New Republic, v.69:no.893:part 2 (1932:Jan. 13)
- Memorandum of Understanding., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Memoranda of Understanding, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: American Red Cross; National War Fund
    Notes: May 1, 1944 through April 30, 1945.
  - Item 2: Memoranda of Understanding, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 1, 1944 through April 30, 1945. Copy 2.
- Memorial Dinners., 1934-1947 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Ten Years in the New York Clothing Manufacturers Exchange, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: CME (Clothing Manufacturers Exchange)
    Notes: April, 1934.
  - Item 2: In Honor of Joseph Schlossberg, General Secretary, ACWA, On His Sixtieth Birthday, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: April 28, 1935.
  - Item 3: 1940 Award to Eleanor Roosevelt on the Occasion of the Seventy-Fifth Anniversary of The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: The Nation
    Notes: May 1, 1940.
  - Item 4: Dinner to Fred Kirchwey on the Occasion of the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of Her Association with The Nation, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: February 27, 1944.
  - Item 5: Tenth Anniversary Dinner: American Labor Party of the State of New York, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: ALP (American Labor Party)
    Notes: May 24, 1946.
  - Item 6: There Are Those Who Remember: A Dinner to Honor the Memory of Franklin Delano Roosevelt, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: National Citizens Political Action Committee
    Notes: April 12, 1946.
  - Item 7: Franklin D. Roosevelt Birthday Memorial Concert, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: The "65 Club"
    Notes: January 30, 1947. Sponsored by the "65 Club"
  - Item 8: Surprise Birthday Dinner in Honor of Hyman Blumberg, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: Independent Laundry Drivers of Greater New York
    Notes: December 12, 1947.
  - Item 9: Dedication of the World Capitol, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Author: United Nations
    Notes: April 13, 1947.
- The Nation., 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  v.150:no.6 (1940:Feb. 10)
  - Item 1: The Nation: Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Number, 1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.150:no.6 (1940:Feb. 10)
- Out of Darkness., Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Out of Darkness Your CIO Dollar Lights Their Way Back, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Profile of a Union., 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Profile of a Union, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Red Cross. Report for the War Period., 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Report for the War Period; January 1, 1942, to February 29, 1944, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Author: American National Red Cross
- The Sentence of the Court., 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Sentence of the Court, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Author: Simon E. Sobeloff
    Notes: Address by Simon E. Sobeloff, Solicitor General of the United States. August 16, 1954.
- The Soviet Union Proposes Peaceful Co-Existence., 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Soviet Union Proposes Peaceful Co-Existence, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Author: National Council of American-Soviet Friendship
    Notes: The End of the Cold War; Banning of Atomic Armaments; Strict International Control and Inspection; Progressive Disarmament. The full text of the proposals submitted to the United Nations on May 10, 1955.
- Toward New Horizons., 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Toward New Horizons: The World Beyond the War, 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Author: Henry A. Wallace; Sumner Welles; John G. Winant; Milo Perkins
- U.S. Congress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: S. 1958 [Report no.573]. A bill to promote equality of bargaining power between employers and employees, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate
    Notes: Calendar no.595.
  - Item 2: Congressional Record. Seventy-First Congress, First Session., 1929; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Author: United States. Congress. House of Representatives.
    Notes: v.71:no.69 (1929:Sept. 29)
- War Department Conference., 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Safeguarding Essential Manpower, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Author: Industrial Personnel Division, Army Service Forces
    Notes: September, 1943.
  - Item 2: List of Guests; War Deparment Conference, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Author: War Department
    Notes: September 27-28, 1943. 15 pages.
  - Item 3: List of Guests; War Deparment Conference, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Notes: September 27-28, 1943. 15 pages. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: List of Guests; War Deparment Conference, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Notes: September 27-28, 1943. 16 pages.
- Correspondence., 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Dear Senator George, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Author: S. Schwob
    Notes: April 8, 1935. Correspondence.
- Hyman Blumberg. Credentials., 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Certificate appointing Hyman Blumberg to Industry Committee no.2, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: December 19, 1938.
  - Item 2: Policy no. GA 2, Certificate no.A, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Author: Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance
    Notes: Blank, canceled form
  - Item 3: Mayor O'Dwyer and the Mayor's Committee, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Author: Grover A. Whalen
    Notes: Telegram
  - Item 4: Industrial Policy Committee charge, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 5: The 26th Biennial Convention, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Author: Frank Rosenblum
    Notes: June 28, 1968. Correspondence.
- ACWA. 19th Biennial Convention., 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. 19th Biennial Convention., 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: News clippings
- Clippings. Baltimore Strike and NRA., 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. Baltimore Strike and NRA., 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Clippings. General., 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Clippings. General., 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Clippings. General., 1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Clippings. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Clippings. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1943; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Clippings. American Labor Party., 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. American Labor Party., 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Clippings. CIO Convention., 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. CIO Convention., 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Clippings. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Clippings. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Clippings. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)